<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Web-things on jellyparks</title><link>https://jellyparks.com/web-things/</link><description>Recent content in Web-things on jellyparks</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:39 +1000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jellyparks.com/web-things/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>saml_overview</title><link>https://jellyparks.com/web-things/saml-overview/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:39 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://jellyparks.com/web-things/saml-overview/</guid><description>What is it According to RFC7522 &amp;ldquo;the Security Assertion Markup Language (SAML) 2.0 is an XML-based framework that alllows identity and security information to be shared across security domains.&amp;rdquo; In a nutshell SAML provides a way to tell a web application you are who you say you are without having to maintain a user/password database within each web application users access. Instead the authentication occurs at a trusted identity provider (IDP) and authorization is left to the web application which people are trying to access once they authenticate with the IDP.</description></item><item><title>xss_ui_redressing</title><link>https://jellyparks.com/web-things/xss-ui-redressing/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:39 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://jellyparks.com/web-things/xss-ui-redressing/</guid><description>Moving Beyond alert(&amp;lsquo;xss&amp;rsquo;) Most people know all about making an alert box pop or getting a cookie sent to an external site with document.cookie. It makes since, it is easy to demo and for the most part makes for a great proof of concept.
Unfortunately these sometimes fail to showcase some of the more potentially devious outcomes from having a site that is vulnerable to XSS.
I recently came across a form of XSS that is called ui redressing.</description></item><item><title>Yogi's Vulnerable SAML app</title><link>https://jellyparks.com/web-things/vulnerable-saml-app/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:39 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://jellyparks.com/web-things/vulnerable-saml-app/</guid><description>What is this thing? I built this app because I wanted to better understand SAML and I wanted to know how to discover, exploit, and remediate vulnearbilities associated with implementations. I created an easily deployable docker environment here that can be spun up on a local machine in about 5 minutes. I also have instructions to split the deployment across multiple hosts.
This includes a fully functional IDP and a Service Provider.</description></item></channel></rss>